New York City
If only everything down there was really as peaceful
as it looks from up here
Yeah, hold it right there
Yeah, like I was saying
you gonna love working down here:
it's cool in the summer and warm in the winter
and no office politics
Oh, sounds better than my last job
I was in the television business
TV? Really?
Hey, my old TV gets this double image
if you know what I mean
Hey, maybe you could...
No, I was a TV executive
Awww!
Then you're better off down here
Holy!..
Oh, it's got me!
Oh! Help!
Aaaaaaaaaa!
Those eyes! They're after me!
What's this?
Another satisfied graduate
of New York City Cab Driving Academy?
Hit the break!
Turn! Turn!
~Night of the Lizard~
subtitles by Nash
and DaQuirm
addic7ed.com
What was that all about
Eyes, red eyes after me
Uh-huh. And did they belong to the little pink elephants?
No, mister, it was real, it was real, I swear!
Yeah, alright, fine!
Just don't let the cops blame this one on me, okay?
The red eyes! The red eyes!
Sure, pal. Whatever you say.
New York City. Never a dull moment